Our Ray of Light
There's an otome game called Our Ray of Light,
also known as ORL.
Our Ray of Light
Playing that game
was a guilty pleasure in my former life.
I met an abrupt end at the age of 18.
But then, the memories of that past life
came rushing back to me in the world of ORL.
Now I live as Pride Royal Ivy,
first-born princess of the Kingdom of Freesia.
I am the elder sister of the game's protagonist, Tiara.
And to her love interests, I am...
a source of tragedy,
the most heretical final boss.
The Cruel Queen
and the Fiancé
Pride?
Are you all right?
If anything's the matter, please let me know.
Thank you, Stale.
Elder Sister, I can't wait until tomorrow!
Neither can I, Tiara.
But... I remain a bit nervous.
I shall do my best to ensure
that your birthday celebration
proceeds without the faintest of issues.
Thank you, Chancellor Gilbert.
Right, tomorrow is my sixteenth birthday celebration.
In this country, women are considered adults
from the age of sixteen.
That's why tomorrow's celebration is a very special day.
If I don't prove I have what it takes to be queen,
or if even the slightest problem occurs,
I'll have more than just bad rumors to contend with.
Rest assured.
When you announce your school system plan,
I'll be right there beside you.
And also...
Actually, I'll save that subject for another time.
Now, if you'll please excuse me.
Stale.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I was just thinking about something.
I'm fine.
Maybe Stale is nervous about tomorrow's festivities, too?
I suppose that's because I'm not the most reliable...
As the first-born princess and heir to the throne,
and as a sister to these two precious souls,
I must avoid making a disgrace of myself tomorrow!
You're way less into this than usual, Stale!
I know...
How many times...
do I have to tell you?
If you've got something to say, then spit it out!
You've been off your game all the time lately!
Tomorrow is my elder sister's birthday celebration.
I know.
I've been appointed as a guard for the event.
She's turning sixteen tomorrow.
And her fiancé will be announced at the celebration, too.
I'm afraid she's forgotten about that.
That's how seriously she's been working on the school system.
No one wants to distract her from that,
so they haven't brought it up.
But...
You knew this would happen, right?
I did.
I've made my peace with it.
I'm prepared to devote my heart and soul, and serve as seneschal,
to both my elder sister and her fiancé.
However...
that's only if I believe Pride's fiancé
is someone worthy of her.
I needed to know,
so I did some digging into Pride's fiancé, personally.
He's the extremely outstanding and distinguished
first-born prince of our allied nation,
the Kingdom of Anemone.
Well, doesn't that sound ideal?
It does.
But...
Rumor has it that he's also a womanizer and a flirt.
To an extreme degree!
First-born prince Leon Adonis Coronaria.
The Kingdom of Anemone's most notorious playboy!
That's who she's getting engaged to!
Elder Sister.
Your announcements of the alliance policy
and the school system went wonderfully.
Thank you.
Not to mention, that dress looks lovely on you!
Doesn't it, Stale?
Uh, yes.
Although, showing less skin might be prudent...
Your Royal Highness Princess Pride,
I wish you the most joyous of birthdays.
Commander Roderick!
You have truly become an admirable princess.
Thank you so much.
Happy birthday to you, Princess Pride.
We are blessed that you were born into our kingdom.
L-Lieutenant Commander Clark!
These two aren't supposed to be love interests, right?
Wait.
That reminds me...
Happy birthday.
I am Callum Bordeaux.
Thank you, Captain Callum.
Your reputation precedes you.
Princess Pride,
I wish you a happy birthday.
Your dress is very pretty.
I mean, not just the dress,
but you are as well.
Thank you, Arthur.
I look forward to your continued service.
Yes.
Of course.
I will protect you always.
Elder Sister!
I-It's nothing, I'm all right.
I suddenly remembered two of the game's love interests!
Wait, if I'm turning sixteen today, that means...
Are you quite well?
Your Royal Highness, Princess Pride.
I deeply apologize for not coming
to pay my respects sooner.
I am Leon Adonis Coronaria,
first-born prince of the Kingdom of Anemone.
I appreciate your kindness.
I am the first-born princess, Pride Royal Ivy.
It is an honor and a pleasure to meet you.
Oh my god.
I can't believe I forgot that
I get engaged on my sixteenth birthday!
Leon.
A love interest in the first installment
of the ORL series, and Queen Pride's—
—that's to say, my fiancé.
Ultimately, he loses everything
and has his heart broken at Pride's hands.
I have never laid my eyes upon someone as beautiful as you.
I do hope our acquaintance will be a long one.
Wait, wait!
Mother hasn't announced anything yet!
What do I do?
He's acting so different from
how he does at the start of the game!
My heart's not ready for this...
Please, call me Leon.
In that case, you may call me Pride.
Shall we head back?
It seems something is about to happen.
"Something"?
Oh, come on! He knows exactly
what's going to happen!
I would like to introduce first-born princess
Pride Royal Ivy's betrothed.
The first-born prince of the Kingdom of Anemone,
Leon Adonis Coronaria.
By his engagement to my beloved daughter Pride,
we shall further strengthen our alliance.
It is an honor.
Princess Pride,
I shall love you with all of my heart.
And with that, my birthday festivities
came to an end without incident.
Leon will spend the next three days
at the castle, then return home.
A week after that, he will come
to fully live in our castle as my fiancé.
The next ten days are very significant.
Both for him, and for me.
Stay away, stay away, stay away!
Stay away, leave me alone!
Don't be like that, Leon.
Your darling, beloved fiancée
is here to pay you a visit.
Hey.
You love me, don't you?
I love you! I love you! I love you! I love you! I love you!
S-S-So please!
I love you, too, you know?
But it really is unfortunate.
You and I haven't actually gotten married yet, have we?
You're the prince consort in name alone
and no one around cares for you a bit.
Say, even the former king of Anemone
told you to never come back, didn't he?
I wonder what will happen to you
if I choose to break off our engagement, hmm?
Oh, that reminds me!
It seems my little sister has been coming here
to spend time with you lately, hmm?
You two sure get along well.
I might have another... jealous fit, you know.
No, I don't feel that way about your sister!
No, no!
I swear, I only love you, Pride!
Just you!
How lovely!
That face you're making... It's my favorite!
Don't fret.
I'll never let you go.
After all,
you're my cute little toy.
Even if you cheat on me again...
I'll always let you alone go unpunished.
No...
No, no...
No, no, no...
Pride, how are you feeling?
I'm fine, thank you.
Though I slept strangely last night...
And how are you, Prince Leon?
I feel quite blessed to see my beloved Pride
starting so bright and early.
Leon is a magnificent prince who has all the skills and temperament needed to become an ideal king.
However, rumors of his philandering have spread far.
This caused him to be ostracized from the Kingdom of Anemone
and engaged to the atrocious
and diabolical Queen Pride.
Ultimately, he is so badly traumatized by Pride
that he develops a severe and intense fear of people.
He loses all status and influence,
becoming a prince in name only.
Understandably, there's absolutely no romance
between Pride and Leon in the game.
Yet...
Shall we take a short rest?
I love you, more than anyone and anything.
There he goes!
The flirt archetype working his magic!
I never stood out in my old life,
and haven't attracted any romantic interest
even after getting reincarnated.
This is just too much for me!
But even so, I have to get a grip.
I need to accept his advances and not shy away.
I have to earn some of his trust before he goes back to his country.
It's okay.
There's no need for me to swoon.
Just forget about being nervous, shy, or anything like that.
After all, the love he murmurs on about...
is all a lie.
Val?!
Sefekh and Khemet are here too!
Hey, Mistress.
Grew up to be pretty good-looking, eh?
Mistress, you're so cute!
Yeah, cute!
Well, you still haven't really filled out much.
Brought you correspondence from the Lilyturf Kingdom.
And a letter of congratulations on your engagement.
So?
What's your fiancé like?
He's wonderful.
What's that thing?
The first-born prince of the Kingdom of Anemone.
I dunno.
It's so awesome!
He's been very kind to me.
I know!
Feeling like runnin' away with us?
I mean, I am your servant and all.
I can easily get you outta the kingdom, if that's what you want me to do.
It ain't so bad, living life on the run.
Free to do whatever you want anywhere in the world.
Using my power to support three kids
would be easy enough.
Is there something funny?
No, I'm sorry.
I just started thinking that living a life
on the run with all of you would actually be nice.
Imagine if the villainous queen just up and vanished,
so Tiara could safely ascend the throne
and have her pick of eligible bachelors.
Like Arthur, Stale, Prince Leon, or the other suitor.
Together, they would lead this kingdom into peace.
But I can't take his hand right now.
I may be the world's worst queen
and heretical final boss, but...
Even so, I've come to love this nation and its people.
I'll fight my fate for as long as I can.
This is where I want to be.
Royalty to the end.
Thanks for the offer, Val.
But I'll keep toughing it out.
Although, if I ever truly lose my place here...
I'd be happy if you'd take me in.
There's no "if" about it.
Just order me to take you in, Princess.
Very well, then.
If that time comes, and you agree to it,
please take me away with you.
Time to go!
Val...
I'm so glad you're in my life.
If the time comes when you seriously wanna ditch everything,
then I'll spend the rest of my life
making sure you all can live.
I'm grateful you've taken me on a tour to so many places.
The Kingdom of Freesia is a lovely nation.
Thank you.
I've heard that you take it upon yourself
to visit the town around your own castle, Prince Leon.
Yes, it's important to know how my people live.
And so, I make it a point to
visit and speak with them personally.
Because being in touch with the people is
the most important thing that a leader like me can do.
What an impressive way of thinking.
Pride, would you like to join me
in gazing up at the starry sky?
Of course.
That must be...
Arthur.
That you, Stale?
Arthur. Prince Leon is—
I...
I hate that Princess Pride is going to marry Prince Leon.
I understand the importance of a royal marriage.
But...
That guy is no good.
He can't make the princess happy.
Arthur, listen to me carefully.
My apologies, but I was wrong.
Prince Leon is a good per—
Well... I won't accept him!
As it stands, that jerk marrying her is...
unacceptable!
Those creepy smiles...
They give me chills!
It's unnatural!
You're telling me that
both Elder Sister and Prince Leon
have been faking their smiles this entire time?
Why, though?
Prince Leon would be one thing,
but why Elder Sister as well?
Well then, Pride, I will see you again soon.
Prince Leon.
What is it?
The promise we made last night...
Please keep it.
Pride...
What did you promise last night?
Well, isn't this grand? All three of the royal siblings
are here to roll out the welcome mat!
The first princess of Lilyturf Kingdom
sent quite the gift for your birthday.
Val!
I have a highly-confidential request for you!
What? Why do I have to?
Yeesh.
Elder Sister...
It's all right.
Yes, everything's fine.
The memories of my past life give me
the insight I need to take action here.
I am the only one...
who can bring Prince Leon happiness.
Every day's unique, you get one chance at it
So you'd better make it count
When people flaunt morality
You've gotta beware they've got their own agenda
Somewhere in your head, there's a voice that's messin' with ya
Don't ever let it turn you 'round
It can't even blow all that hot air it's full of
Get yourself in gear and live however you wanna
Live so fast that the claws of despair will languish in your dust
And you'll be the one with an agenda that they'll all see as just
Keep on shouldering the world around you
Keep on doubting every thought that's bound you
If things go awry, keep pushing through and know that everything'll work in the end
If you find it's in your power to change the world
I'm sure you can make the future bright
We'll blaze on ahead until we track down the route we want to take
We'll keep trying every door until we find one that goes our way
The Most Heretical Last Boss Queen:
From Villainess to Savior.
Episode 2: "The Cruel Queen Speaks".
The Cruel Queen Speaks